Welcome to Bakudan Ramen Links Hub Admin. Sign in with your admin credentials.
Dashboard: Action Required alerts, KPI tiles, Quick Actions, and Pages Overview.
Pages: control center. Green badge = public Customer Link Hub. Purple = private Staff Training.
Buttons tab: manage every button. Save as Template, drag to reorder, toggle Visible, Enabled, Featured.
Sections tab: group buttons under headers like Order Online or Rewards.
Page Settings: title, URL slug, visibility, SEO. Google preview updates live.
Templates: save a page as Template once, reuse for new stores in one click.
Campaigns: track marketing initiatives. Clicks roll up from all shortlinks.
UTM Builder: track which channel drives clicks. Copy URL or create Shortlink plus QR.
QR and Shortlinks: library of all shortlinks with QR images and click counts.
Customer Service: post temporary Service Notices as banners on the public Link Hub.
Staff Training: private page, unlisted, no index. Internal Use Only.
Scheduling: combined calendar view of everything with start or end dates.
Blog: write posts with ready-made templates. Rich text editor with emoji.
Locations: single source of truth for phone, address, Toast links, and hours.
SEO Manager: overview of every page SEO. Red alerts for missing fields.
Link Health: checks links periodically for broken, redirected, or timed out URLs.
Analytics: real page view and click numbers. Views and clicks in 24 hours.
Audit Log: every change recorded with who did what and when.
Settings: Instagram and Facebook links, headline text, marketing copy.
That completes the tour. Core modules are live today. Thank you for watching.