Welcome to Bakudan Ramen Links Hub Admin. Manage everything customers see from one place. No coding required.
Dashboard: a quick overview. Action Required alerts real issues. KPI tiles show live button counts and clicks. Quick Actions give one-click access.
Pages: control center for every page. Green badge means public Customer Link Hub. Purple badge means private Staff Training. Click Edit to open.
Buttons tab: manage every button. Save as Template to reuse a page structure. Drag and drop to reorder. Each button has Visible, Enabled, Featured toggles.
Destination Types: External Website, Phone, Email, Maps. Toast Online Ordering. Call This Location auto-fills from your Locations data.
Sections: group buttons like Order Online or Rewards headers. Every button belongs to one section. Create, rename, reorder, hide, schedule, or delete.
Page Settings: title, URL slug, visibility, SEO. Google preview updates live as you type. Character counters for SEO title and meta description.
Templates: save a page as Template once, reuse for new stores. Create Page from Template in one click with title and slug.
Campaigns: track marketing initiatives across shortlinks. Clicks roll up from all shortlinks. Delete a campaign and its shortlinks still work.
UTM Builder: track which channel drives clicks. Preview URL updates live. Copy URL or create Shortlink plus QR code. Changing destination does not change QR image.
QR and Shortlinks: library of all shortlinks. Each has QR image, click count, and active status. Download QR as PNG.
Locations: single source of truth for The Rim, Stone Oak, Bandera. Phone, address, Toast links, hours. Call This Location reads from here.
Staff Training: private page. Works like Customer Link Hub but is unlisted, no index, and never appears on public pages. Internal Use Only.
Scheduling: combined calendar view of everything with start or end dates. See which pages are about to go live or expire.
Blog Composer: write posts with ready-made templates. Rich text editor with emoji. Social caption and hashtags. Schedule auto-publish.
SEO Manager: overview of every page SEO. Red alerts for missing title or description. One-click Edit to fix.
Analytics: real page view and click numbers. Total buttons, live versus hidden, views and clicks in 24 hours.
Settings: global Instagram and Facebook links, headline text, marketing copy. Users: Super Admin, Marketing Manager, Store Manager, Viewer.
Customer Service: post temporary Service Notices as banners. Set type, scope, start and end dates. Note: Admin create and edit currently saves locally in the browser.
Audit Log: every change is recorded with who did what and when. If something looks wrong, check here first.
That completes the tour. Core modules are live today. Forms, Automations, and Media Library are partially functional. Thank you for watching.